Matchmaker Santa is a tv movie, comedy, drama
film directed by David S. Cass Sr..
As a little girl, Melanie Hogan wished to find her own prince
charming just like her parents found true love.
Now an adult, Melanie is running her own bakery
and dating a handsome CEO, Justin.
Although things seem perfect when Justin asks Melanie to spend the holidays
together at his beautiful lake house upstate—and meet his mother.
Melanie finds herself spending more time with Justin’s best friend and loyal
assistant, Dean, who just might be harboring a secret crush on her.
When complications arise that throw Melanie and Dean together over
the holiday, will the two realize they're meant to be?
Melanie "Skeeter" Hogan, played by Lacey Chabert.
Dean Ford, played by Adam Mayfield.
Young Melanie, played by Nikki Hahn.
Blaire, played by Elizabeth Ann Bennett.
Peggy, played by Florence Henderson.
Jack Tisdale, played by Robert Pine.
Sofia Nicole Hahn (born November 13, 2002) is an American actress.
She is known for her role as Emily Cooper in Adventures in
Babysitting, among other television roles.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.